I'm Ivan Madar.
Maintenance of a facility, obviously, it's not that complicated.
We know what we have to do to maintain the heating and air conditioning and the plumbing in here.
The question becomes: do you have the in-house staff that does all these repairs when necessary, or do you hire contractors?
I tend to have one person on staff, depending on the size of the facility, obviously, but at least one person who is a universal handyman, who can fix everything, except the large, large jobs.
That person should be available to the facility for at least two shifts.
Meaning about sixteen hours a day.
So whenever something breaks, you have to fix it right away.
In a private club, it is not acceptable that things are broken for longer than necessary, and it's usually only a few hours, or at the most, one day to the next.
If things linger and are not repaired then it creates the tremendous dissatisfaction on the part of the members or our guest visiting the resort.
So it's important to fix it right away.
There's nothing more distressing when you walk in, let's say in a fitness area, and every other treadmill has a sign on it, it's out of operation.
If you do put a sign on something that it's out of operation, it should be dated and it should state when it's going to be repaired so people don't come and just wonder what is going to happen.
Those are kind of basic principles of good relations with the members and the staff, your maintenance staff.